sixbid.com 2017-07-07

# SIXBID.COM - Experts in numismatic Auctions

**Data Security: Our Privacy Policy**  
  
We at Sixbid AG take the security of your information very seriously and adhere strictly to data protection laws. We collect personal information through this site only when necessary and when provided to us by our customers. In no cases will this data be sold or otherwise transferred to any third party without your consent.  
  
The following statements include the type of information we collect and how we protect your data.

**Data Processing on this Internet Site**  
  
Sixbid AG automatically stores information in its server logs that is sent by a user’s browser. This information includes:  
  
• Browser type and version  
• Operating system  
• Referrer URL (previously visited page)  
• Hostname and IP address   
• Time the site is accessed  
  
This data is not personally identifiable, and Sixbid AG does not try to assign it to any individual. Also, we do not compile the data with other information, and all personal information is deleted before any statistical analysis.

**Cookies**  
  
Sixbid.com uses cookies on some of its pages. These are small text files placed on your computer that help the Web server identify you and offer you a safer, more efficient, and more accessible browsing experience. Most of these cookies are “session cookies,” which last only until you close your browser. Cookies do no harm to your computer and do not contain viruses.

**Data Storage Law**  
  
You have the right to know what information is being stored about you, how it was obtained, and what its purpose is. Information on this stored data is maintained by the data security officer of Sixbid AG.

**Further Information**  
  
Your trust is important to us. Therefore, we are happy to talk to you about the storage and processing of personal data. If you have any questions, or this privacy policy does not address your concerns, please contact the data security officer of Sixbid AG.  
  
We are not responsible for the content of any external links.
